Thank you.
You got the informations out of a patent.
Okay.
Makes normally sense to show also the patent because if you show it like that, so for me, I don't know what's 27, 28 or something like that, so I'm not so deep into the patent.
So it's only a side fact. Maybe you can go to slide number six, I guess it was six with the decisions.
Thank you.
Thank you. Yes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Now it makes sense.
Okay.
We can go on with slide number six, I guess.
There you need a decision from my person.
To the presentation, yeah.
I see the patent at the moment.
Yes, so P totally fine, so end-of-line testing.
Thank you.
Okay.
It depends.
So I guess you have to dig there a little bit deeper and then you will find informations,
but yeah, it's up to you.
So the most important point is that you feel good about the topic.
So I guess we can do from every topic a good thesis, but the most important point is that
you take a decision and you feel comfortable with that decision and you also can explain
it.
If you have an explanation tree or something like that, so that would be very important
and then it's totally fine.
Okay, from my point of view, it's also totally fine.
Perfect.
Do you need an answer from my side or decision from my side?
Yes.
Thank you.
That should be enough. The case that you do not find so many information is more or less a good case
because that means that there is still a lot of space for research. So maybe we can take the details
from a different industry to bring it up or to transfer it to the battery industry. You know what
I mean? So especially, yeah, no, no, no, I'm totally fine. So I was ready.
Thank you.
Yeah, fake news are not the best news.
Yeah, it depends, you can dig there.
And if you say, okay, there is nothing, then it's, of course, difficult, but normally you
can transfer the information.
So you can say what is, or you can summarize the attributes about robotic, humanoid robotics
and say, okay, that is possible, that is not possible.
And you can use it in that kind of area.
You can't use it in that kind of area because of, so there, it could be possible.
Perfect.
Do we have more questions?
Perfect, sounds like a plan.
Let's do it like that.
Perfect.
I would say, yeah.
So yes, we have to start or we can do it next week.
So I will share you the information.
So we need an abstract.
So one or two slides or one or two pages with some informations about the topic and the
rest, and then we can can register the thesis and start.
Perfect.
Yeah, you're welcome.
You too.
Bye-bye.